Guide to the Claire Kincannon theatre collection, 1955-2011
George Mason University Libraries
Claire Kincannon theatre collection
1955-2011
C0018
George Mason University Special Collections & Archives
20.0 Linear feet (40 boxes)
This collection contains promotional materials for plays in the Washington, D.C., area, including programs, photographs, and press kits as well as a selection of programs and playbills from theaters in New York, London, and regional theaters in Ohio dating back to 1955, as well as some limited film-related materials. In addition to paper materials there are also audio visual materials featuring Kincannon's radio show Behind the Scenes and a project on Hungary.
Lois Claire Kincannon
Alternative Form Available
All of the "Behind the Scenes with Claire Kincannon" shows on audiotape are available in digital format.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Claire Kincannon in 2007-2008 and 2011.
Biographical Information
Claire Kincannon graduated from the University of Michigan's College of Architecture and Design and pursued a career in Interior Architecture. In 1972, she became a radio journalist and theatre critic in the Washington, D.C., area, starring in her own radio program, Behind the Scenes. It was during this time that she worked as a theatre critic, reviewing the performances she attended on her radio show. She moved to Paris, France in late 1992 with her husband, eventually returning in 2000. She founded Dancing Ink Press while in Paris, using it to publish several books including Paeonian to Paris, Sheets for Men Only, Sheets to the Wind, and Rockin' with Porch Memories. She still lives in the Washington, D.C., area and continues to write books and exhibit artwork.
Scope and Content
The Claire Kincannon theatre collection represents a lifetime and a career of theatre appreciation and attendance. Materials that comprise this collection track Kincannon's attendance at area performances in Ohio (1955-1982) and on Broadway (1955-2007), as well as her work as a theatre critic in Washington, D.C. (1971-2011).
The collection includes programs, press releases, photographs, and other outreach materials of various theatre productions. Also included in the collection are ticket stubs, invitations, schedules, and advertisements for certain productions. Some of the programs also contain the hand-written notes of Kincannon from when she worked as a critic; these notes provide unique insights into the job of a critic. There are also marketing releases for motion pictures, including photographs, press releases, and "behind the scenes" information.
Many of the programs are from the Kennedy Center, the National Theatre, Arena Stage, The Folger Theatre, Wolf Trap Farm Park, and other various theaters in the D.C. area. Also included in the collection are productions by the Kenley Players and Victory Theatre in Dayton, OH, among others in the area. The Broadway collection encompasses several theaters' productions.
The first series covers Kincannon's time as a critic in Washington, D.C., from 1971-2008. This series contains programs, press releases, photographs, and other behind the scenes and marketing information. The second series covers Kincannon's early interest in theatre while in the Ohio area (1955-1982). It contains mostly playbooks and programs from area performances. The third series is the collection of Broadway and London productions Kincannon attended from 1955-2007. This series consists of mostly playbills and programs. The fourth series is film-related materials from 1956-1992, consisting of souvenir books, magazines, and press packets relating to each film. The fifth series is audiovisual materials from 1983-1992, consisting of reel-to-reel audiotapes, audiotape cartridges, and videocassettes. Much of the material is from the Behind the Scenes with Claire Kincannon radio program. Behind the Scenes was a three-minute feature on the performing arts, and was available via the Public Radio Satellite System.
Arrangement
Organized into five series.
Series 1: Washington, D.C., 1971-2008 (Boxes 1-20, 28, 30, 32, 33)
Series 2: Ohio Regional Theatres, 1955-1982 (Boxes 21-24, 31)
Series 3: Broadway and London Productions, 1955-2007 (Boxes 25-27)
Series 4: Film-related Materials, 1956-1992 (Box 29)
Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1983-1986 (Boxes 34-40)
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds many other theatre collections.
Index Terms
Persons:
Kincannon, Lois Claire.
Subjects:
Motion pictures.; Theater--England--London.; Theater--New York (State)--New York.; Theater--Ohio.; Theater--Washington (D.C.)
Document Types:
Live sound recordings.; Photographic prints.; Sound recordings.; Video recordings.
- Series 1: Washington, D.C., 1971-2011; (24 boxes)
  Scope and Contents note
  The first series covers Kincannon's time as a critic in Washington, D.C. from 1971-2008. This series contains programs, press releases, photographs, and other behind the scenes and marketing information.
  - Performer Magazine, Filene Center, Wolf Trap, July, August, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Program for multiple performances.
  - The United States Field Band, circa 1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Press packet. Ten photographs.
  - Kiss Me Kate, Wayside Theatre, August, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Program.
  - The Misanthrope, Kennedy Center, February, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Production of the National Theatre of Great Britain. Stagebill.
  - Living Stage Theatre, 1975-1987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Documents regarding workshops. Press releases.
  - Luv, Wayside Theatre, June, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Invitation; Program, photographs.
  - Living Stage Jams Index, 1978-1981 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Banjo Dancing, Arena Stage, ca. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gypsy, Octorian Theatre Co., Spring 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cabaret, Blue Ridge Alliance of the Performing Arts, Spring 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Choir, Woolly Mammoth Theatre Company, March 18, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photograph; Program.
  - Guys and Dolls, National Theatre, March 9, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Pirates of Penzance, National Theatre, March, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Medea, Kennedy Center, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Stagebill.
  - Les Contes d'Hoffmann, Kennedy Center, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Production of the New York Metropolitan Opera. Stagebill.
  - American College Theatre Festival XIV, Kennedy Center, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Company, Reston Community Players, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, Reston Community Players, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Shiro, Kennedy Center, May, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Production of the Tokyo Kid Brothers. Stagebill.
  - The Dining Room, Kennedy Center, June, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace, Wayside Theatre, July, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - A Chorus Line, Wolf Trap, August, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Season 1982-1983, Folger Theatre, ca. 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Preview Materials.
  - The Merchant of Venice, Folger Theatre Group, September, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Annie, Kennedy Center, September, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Twice Around the Park, Kennedy Center, September, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Flying Karamozov Brothers Vol. 2, Arena Stage, October, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Monday After the Miracle, Kennedy Center, October, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Stagebill; Photograph.
  - New York City Ballet, Kennedy Center, October, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Oklahoma, Blue Ridge Alliance of the Performing Arts, November, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Pajama Game, Reston Community Players, November, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - A Medieval Christmas Pageant, Folger Theatre Group, November 30, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Outrage, Kennedy Center, December, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - On Your Toes, Kennedy Center-ANTA, December, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Animal Crackers, and Trinidad Sisters, Arena Stage, 1982, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Two photographs.
  - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom: A Curriculum Guide for training teachers, Living Stage Theatre, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - American Ballet Theatre, Kennedy Center, January, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - She Stoops to Conquer, Folger Theatre, January 18, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    News Release; Program.
  - The Imaginary Invalid, Arena Stage, January 21, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Press Release; Program.
  - Screenplay, Arena Stage, February 4, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Marriage A La Mode, Folger Theatre, March 8, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - And They Dance Real Slow in Jackson, New Playwrights Theatre, March 22, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Press Release; Program; Photograph.
  - Geniuses, Arena Stage, March 25, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Master Harold...and the boys, Warner Theatre, April, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Buried Child, Arena Stage, April 15, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Invitation; Program.
  - All's Well That Ends Well, Folger Theatre, April, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Make and Break, Kennedy Center, April, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - American College Theatre Festival XV, Kennedy Center, April, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Adriana Lecouvreur, Kennedy Center, April, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Production of the Metropolitan Opera. Stagebill.
  - Rain, Waterford School, April 6, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Stop the World...I Want to Get Off, Blue Ridge Alliance of the Performing Arts, April, May, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Lena Horne: The Lady and Her Music, Warner Theatre, April, May, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Program. Photograph.
  - Porgy and Bess, Kennedy Center, May, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dancin' in the Street!, Ford's Theatre, May 3, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Invitation; Program; Photograph.
  - Candide, Arena Stage, May 13, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bluegrass Benefit, Loudoun County, May 14, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Black Coffee, Wayside Theatre, June, July, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The Mikado, Blue Ridge Alliance of Performing Arts, July, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Greater Tuna, Kennedy Center, July, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Corn is Green, Kennedy Center, July, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Production of the Elizabeth Theatre Group. Stagebill.
  - On Golden Pond, Wayside Theatre, July, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Private Lives, Kennedy Center, August, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - A Soldier's Play, Ford's Theatre, October, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Noises Off, Kennedy Center, October, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Beyond Therapy, Arena Stage, October 28, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cinderella, Folger Theatre, November, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The Wiz, Warner Theatre, November, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - As You Like It, Arena Stage, November 25, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Donor list; Program.
  - Agnes of God, Kennedy Center, December, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Symphonie Concertante, Kennedy Center, December 6, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Production of the American Ballet Theatre. Stagebill.
  - Cinderella, Kennedy Center, December 20, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Washington DC playbills, 1983-2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    James Joyce's The Dead, Kennedy Center
    Native Storyteller: Ron Ki-Ke-In Hamilton (Nuu-Chah-Nulth), Smithsonian
    Our Town, Arena Stage
    She Always Said, Pablo, Kennedy Center
    Still Life, Arena Stage
  - Waiting in Vain, The Living Stage, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Press packet.
  - School for Scandal, Folger Theatre, January, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - The Hasty Heart, Kennedy Center, January, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Stagebill. Photograph.
  - Woman of the Year, Kennedy Center, January, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 42nd Street, National Theatre, January, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Flesh Eaters, New Playwrights Theatre, January, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Program; Two Photographs.
  - The Father, Source Theatre Company, January, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Program; Invitation.
  - A Cry of Players, Source Theatre Company, January, February, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Three Sisters, Arena Stage, January 20, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Talking with..., Horizons Theatre, February, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Accidental Death of an Anarchist, Arena Stage, February 3, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Invitation; Photograph; Program.
  - Lyndon, Kennedy Center, February, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Death of a Salesman, Kennedy Center, February, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - New York City Ballet, Kennedy Center, February, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Canterbury Tales, Ford's Theatre, February 14, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Auntie Mame, Blue Ridge Alliance of the Performing Arts, March, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - The Mayor of Zalamea, Folger Theatre, March, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Follies, Hexagon at Trinity Theatre, March 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - End of the World with Symposium to Follow, Kennedy Center, March, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Long Day's Journey into Night, Source Theatre Company, March, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - The Library of Congress Talent Show, New Playwrights Theatre, March, April, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Program; Photograph.
  - No Exit, Source Theatre Company, March, April, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Program; Two photographs.
  - Quartermaine's Terms, Arena Stage, March 9, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Oliver, Warner Theatre, March 22, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cloud 9, Arena Stage, March 30, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Cloud 9 and Happy End, Arena Stage, ca. 1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    35mm slides.
  - Nine, Kennedy Center, April, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Ernani and Die Walkure, Kennedy Center, April, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - The Fourth Annual Richard L. Coe Award, Kennedy Center, April 1, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Cats, National Theatre, May, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - The Madwoman of Chaillot, Round House Theatre, May, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Henry V, Folger Theatre, May 8, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - George M, Shenandoah Summer Music Theatre, Summer, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Shenandoah Summer Music Theatre, Summer, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Crimes of the Heart, Olney Theatre, June 5, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Ticket stub; Program; 35mm Slides.
  - Foolfire, Arena Stage, June 7, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Jerry's Girls, Kennedy Center, June, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Gardenia and Lydie Breeze, New Playwrights Theatre, June, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Twain or "Spect It Ain't the Truth", Round House Theatre, June 25, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Other Places, New Arts Theatre, July, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Coronation of Poppea, Wolf Trap Opera Company, July, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - A Quiet Place and Trouble in Tahiti, Kennedy Center, July, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Production of the Houston Grand Opera and Teatro alla Scala. Stagebill; Photograph.
  - The Gin Game, Olney Theatre, July 3, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Do Black Patent Leather Shoes Really Reflect Up?, Olney Theatre, August 28, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1984-1985 Season Preview, Folger Theatre (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Brochure.
  - King Lear, Folger Theatre, September, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Master Class, Kennedy Center, September, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Zorba, Kennedy Center, September, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire, Source Theatre Company, September, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Will Roger's U.S.A., Ford's Theatre, September 11, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Nest of the Wood Grouse, Kennedy Center, October, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Production of the New York Shakespeare Festival. Stagebill; Photograph.
  - Burial Customs, New Playwrights Theatre, October, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - America Hurrah, Woolly Mammoth Theatre Company, October, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Photograph.
  - The Tempest, Arena Stage, October 5, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Alleum, Studio Theatre, October 31, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Crossed Words, Folger Theatre, November, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - The Beautiful Lady, New Playwrights Theatre, November, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Sugar Babies, Warner Theatre, November 7, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - The Gospel at Colonus, Arena Stage, November 23, 2984 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Twenty Seven Wagons Full of Cotton and The Shock of Recognition, Blue Ridge Alliance of the Performing Arts, December 1984 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dracula, Kennedy Center, December 1984 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Production of the Paramount Theatre Prod. Stagebill.
  - Brighton Beach Memoirs, National Theatre, December 1984 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Passion Play, Arena Stage, December 7, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Spoleto Festival, Charleston, South Carolina, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Balletap U.S.A., Ford's Theatre, January, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Orgasmo Adulto Escapes from the Zoo, Horizon's Theatre, January, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Odd Couple, National Theatre, January, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Twelfth Night or What You Will, Source Theatre Company, January, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Busboy, Source Theatre Company, January, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Much Ado About Nothing and Cyrano de Bergerac, Kennedy Center, January, February, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Production of the Royal Shakespeare Company. Stagebill; Three photographs.
  - Man and Superman, Arena Stage, January 11, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Waiting for Godot, Round House Theatre, January 11, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, Folger Theatre, January 15, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Outside Waco, Hudson Guild Theatre, January 30, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Showbill.
  - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men, Ford's Theatre, February, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Tom Jones, Hayloft Professional Dinner Theatre, February, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Real Estate, Arena Stage, February 8, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Henry IV Part I, Kennedy Center, March, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - My One and Only, Kennedy Center, March, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Production of the Opera House; Three Photographs; Stagebill.
  - The Real Inspector Hound and After Magritte, Reston Community Players, March 1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Bald Soprano and The Lesson, Source Theatre Company, March, April, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tartuffe, Arena Stage, March 8, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hamlet, Folger Theatre, March 19, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Invitation; Program; Two Photographs.
  - Last Days at the Dixie Girl Cafe, Horizon's Theatre, April, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - American College Theatre Festival XVII, Kennedy Center, April, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Press Release, Wolf Trap, April 16, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Press Release.
  - Isn't It Romantic, Arena Stage, April 26, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Mark Twain Tonight, Kennedy Center, May, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Count of Monte Cristo, Kennedy Center, May, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Flyer; Stagebill.
  - The Real Thing, National Theatre, May, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - The 1940's Radio Hour, Round House Theatre, May 3, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Spalding Gray, New Playwrights Theatre, May 5, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Execution of Justice, Arena Stage, May 10, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Helen Hayes Awards, National Theatre, May 13, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Program; Press Release; Newspaper Articles.
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, Folger Theatre, May 14, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - The American Film Festival: Salute to Hollywood Musicals, Charleston County Library, May, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Presented by Piccolo Spoleto. Program.
  - Ariodante, Dock Street Theatre, May, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Presented by the Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC. Program.
  - Ballet Eddy Toussaint de Montreal, Gaillard Municipal Auditorium, May, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - La Fanciulla del West, Gaillard Municipal Auditorium, May, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tent Meeting, Dock Street Theatre, May, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Presented by the Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC. Program. Festival Brochures; Travel Aids; Postcard.
  - New Voices, Horizons Theatre, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - This is the House, Horizon Theatre, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Production of the Human Bridge Theater Company. Press Kit.
  - Coyote Ugly, Kennedy Center, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Danny and the Deep Blue Sea, New Arts Theatre, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Goldberg Variations, Spoleto, Charleston, SC, June, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Painting Churches, Olney Theatre, July 9, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Program; Press Release; Notes.
  - New York City Ballet, Kennedy Center, September, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - La Cage aux Folles, National Theatre, September 18, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Photograph; Tickets; Stagebill.
  - Playing for Time, Studio Theatre, September 18, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Handy Dandy, Ford's Theatre, September 23, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Thin Wall, New Playwrights Theatre, October, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Extremities, Source Theatre Company, October, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Othello, Folger Theatre, October 1, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - The Foreigner, Olney Theatre, October 1, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - The Good Person of Setzuan, Arena Stage, October 4, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Invitation; Program; Four slides.
  - Fool for Love, Round House Theatre, October 4, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 'Night Mother, Arena Stage, October 12, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Little Me, Ford's Theatre, November, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Lillian, Kennedy Center, November, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Is This Real? and Solo Voyages, New Playwrights Theatre, November, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Two Photographs.
  - A Walk Out of Water, Studio Theatre, November 20, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - The Man Who Killed the Buddha, Round House Theatre, November 22, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Women and Water, Arena Stage, November 29, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - A Seagull, Kennedy Center, December, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Production of the American National Theatre. Stagebill.
  - Aren't We All?, Kennedy Center, December, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - The Merry Wives of Windsor, The Shakespeare Theatre at The Folger, December 1985 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Humana Festival, Classics in Context, Actor's Theatre of Louisville, KY, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Programs; Invitations; Louisville guide; Notes.
  - Automatic Pilot, Horizons Theatre, January, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Zorba, National Theatre, January, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Beyond Therapy, Source Theatre Company, January, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Sally and Marsha, Round House Theatre, January 10, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Restoration, Arena Stage, January 17, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jeeves Takes Charge, Ford's Theatre, February, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Idiot's Delight, Kennedy Center, February, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - The Cherry Orchard, The Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, February 25, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - The Wild Duck, Arena Stage, February 28, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Social Security, National Theatre, March, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Long Day's Journey into Night, National Theatre, March, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - The Birthday Party, Studio Theatre, March 12, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - The Philadelphia Story, Arena Stage, March 21, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hay Fever, Kennedy Center, April, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Dream Girls, National Theatre, April, May, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Stagebill; Press Release.
  - Johnny Bull, Horizons Theatre, April, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Hot Mikado, Ford's Theatre, April 1, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Program; Tickets.
  - Brotherhood, New Playwrights Theatre, April 3, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Two Photographs; Program.